assurant.com 2017-02-16

# Privacy Policy - Assurant

Assurant, Inc. understands that privacy is important to our customers and we strive to “Protect What Matters Most.” This Privacy Notice explains how we collect, use, and share the personal information we collect on this website. This Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to protect your  personal information and how you can reach us to answer any questions you may have about  Assurant’s privacy practices.

**  
Information We Collect and How We Use It**

_**Personal Information You Provide**_    
  
You may choose to provide personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address on the Assurant, Inc. website (Site).  

_**Event Registration**_

You may register on our Site for Assurant events.  You may provide us with information such as your name, email address, company and industry affiliation when registering for an event. We use this information to register you for the event and contact you about changes and updates regarding the event. We also may use the information to communicate with you about other events and topics that we believe may be of interest to you. 

_**News and Alerts**_

On our Site, you may sign up to receive news and alerts from Assurant, Inc. To sign up, we may ask you for your name, company, job title, phone number,  and  email address.  We use the information you provide to send you the communications you request. We also may use the information to communicate with you about other topics that we believe may be of interest to you. **_

Email Assurant

_**

You may want to submit comments or questions to Assurant, Inc. You will be asked to provide certain personal information, including, when applicable, type of policy, policy number, reason/topic, name email address, phone number, and address. We may use this information to identify you as a customer and direct your comment or question to the appropriate Assurant business unit. To protect your privacy, please do not email us information you consider confidential.  Email is not a secure method of communication and is not encrypted.

_**Careers**_

You may submit your resume and other information to apply for a job with Assurant. We use the information you submit in connection with your job inquiry. 

_**Other Site Features**_ ** _  
_**  
Our Sites offer various features, which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personal information so we can provide you with and communicate with you about these features. 

**_Other Uses of your personal information_**  

We may use the personal information you provide on the Sites for our internal purposes. These purposes include administration of the Site, market research, data analytics and compliance with our legal obligations, policies and procedures.

_**Personal Information We Collect by Automated Means  
**_  
We use a variety of commonly used technologies, like cookies to understand how you use the Site, to make our services safer, and easier to use and to help create a better and more personalized experience for you. These technologies and the information we collect are listed below. ** _  
_**

_Cookies_

Like many companies, some of our Site may use “cookies.” Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites. We may use cookies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited us before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify site features in which you may have the greatest interest. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting our Site.

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this Site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this Site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information.

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note that some features may not function properly if you decide to not accept cookies.

_Web Beacons_

Certain pages on our Site may contain “web beacons” (also know as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party. 

_IP Addresses_

An IP address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our Site, we may view the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general physical location of the device and understand from what geographic regions our website visitors come. We also may use this information to enhance and/or tailor our Sites.

_Browser or device:_ _  
_  
Certain information is collected by most browsers and/or through your device, such as your operating system version, internet browser type and version, device type, and screen resolution. We could use this information to ensure our Sites are functioning properly and for  security purposes.

_Flash objects:_

Certain pages on our Site may contain Adobe Flash objects (also known as “Local Shared Objects”). You can learn more about Flash objects and how to control and/or disable them by visiting the Adobe website. If you choose to disable Flash objects from our Site, then you may not be able to benefit from the information and/or services offered. 

To opt-out of generic data collection services, visit the following website:  

  * For more information and opt-out options regarding ClickTale, <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>[ ](http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html)

**  
Information We Share**

We do not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose your personal information submitted through our Site, except as described in this Privacy Notice. We may share your information with any of the Assurant affiliated companies. We also may share the information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or pursuant to legal process, (ii) in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.  

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information you have provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.  
**  
Our Security Procedures**  

We restrict access to customer information to those employees whom we know have a valid business purpose to have access to such data. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards. We require those who provide services for us and to whom we provide your data to implement the same safeguards.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes, we will provide current customers a new notice that describes our new practices and will post it on our Internet websites.

**"Do not track" signals**

We do not respond to a web browser’s “do not track” signal or other mechanisms that signal a request that our site not track the consumer’s online activities over time and across websites. Other parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Site.

**Process for reviewing or requesting changes to personal information**

If you think that any personal information we have collected about you is inaccurate, you may send a written request for review to us at the address provided below.  We will investigate your request and make appropriate changes if warranted.

**Links to other websites**

This website may contain links to other websites that may have online information practices different from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy and security practices of those websites, and we encourage our visitors to learn about the privacy and security practices of those websites.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. For more information about protecting your child's privacy online, visit the Federal Trade Commission website.

**Privacy contact information**

We welcome your questions or comments regarding this online Privacy Policy. Please write to The Assurant, Attention Assurant Privacy Officer, Assurant, Inc. One Chase Manhattan Plaza, New York, NY 10005 or e-mail us your question to [contact_corpcomm@assurant.com](mailto:contact_corpcomm@assurant.com)
